So what should I photograph?
じゃあ、何撮る?
I want this in.
これが入りたいです
Well, it's a popular one.
あれね、人気のやつね
Just try your best.
ちょっと頑張って
I never take pictures.
絶対撮らない
I went to a strange place, a strange place.
変なとこ行った、変なとこ
It's no good if you don't aim for this ring.
この輪っか狙わないとダメなんだよ
Now I'm trying to take the box by force.
箱今は無理やり取ろうとしてる
It hit me in a weird place.
変なとこ刺した
It hit me in a really weird place.
すげー変なとこ刺した
This is difficult.
難しいね、これね
This is really fun.
これすげー楽しいやつじゃん
It's really strong.
めっちゃ強いですよ
Is it strong?
強いの?
Have you ever done it?
やったことあるの?
Really.
本当に
It happened many times.
何回もありました
How to press the button now.
今のボタンの押し方
This was interesting.
面白かったね、これね
I went.
いけた
敗北、敗北
I hit Taiko and said "Sir".
タイコー叩いてサーってなってるよ
Hit Taiko.
タイコー叩いて
Taiko looks like he's good, hey.
タイコーうまそうな顔してるよ、ちょっと
It's nostalgic.
懐かしいね
You can go with this.
これでいけます
It's going well, isn't it?
なんかうまくね?
Isn't it amazing?
めっちゃすごくないですか?
He's a professional.
プロやん
Did you say that it can't be helped?
なんかしょうもないってことは出した?
I did my best.
頑張りました
That's amazing.
すげーな
I've only removed about two.
2個くらいしか外してないんだよ
surely.
確かに
You haven't been practicing, have you?
練習してないでしょ?
I haven't practiced.
練習してないです
You have it at home, right?
家にあるでしょ、
this.
これ
Wannasu-chan.
ワ ナスちゃん
yes.
はい
It’s been a while since I went to karaoke?
カラオケ久しぶり?
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
Don't you come often?
あんま来ないの?
karaoke.
カラオケ
It didn't come at all.
全然来てなかったです
why?
なんで?
I could sing.
歌えたな
歌えたです
What do you always sing?
いつも何を歌うの?
There are many such as Nogizaka.
ノギザカとかが多いです
Nogizaka?
ノギザカ?
It looks like Nogizaka.
ノギザカいそうだもんね
Wannasu-chan, at karaoke or something.
ワナスちゃんさ、カラオケとかでさ、
Are there no naughty episodes?
エッチなエピソードがないの?
I've never practiced.
練習したことないです
Have you never practiced?
練習したことないんだ?
Eh.
えー
Is this something you have practiced?
練習したことなのかな?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
I don't have any experience.
経験ないもんね
So, try turning it into a regular sports field.
そこでさ、普通に体育場にしてみて
I've been photographed, what do you think?
撮られちゃってるけど、どう?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Opened.
開いた
And then another cute person entered.
そしてまた可愛い人に入ってきたね
衝動
Styron is thick.
スタイロンが厚いんだね
Look back.
後ろ向いてみて
Try lifting your skirt.
そのままスカート上げてみて
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's digging into your butt.
お尻に食い込んじゃってるね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Because it's really digging into me.
すごい食い込んでるから
I think it's really cute.
すごい可愛いと思う
Look this way.
こっち向いて
I'm getting nervous.
緊張しちゃうね
That's what I got photographed.
あんなん撮られてね
What kind of bra did you wear?
ブラジャーどんなのしてきたの?
Sit down again for a moment.
ちょっともう一回座って
Go ahead and take your best shot.
もうさ、ベスト撮ってみて
If you find a friend, you'll be angry.
友達見つかったら怒られちゃうね
This is cute.
これ可愛いね
Isn't it illegal?
反則級じゃない?
this.
これ
It's super cute.
超可愛いんだよね
Then just unbutton that button.
じゃあそのボタンちょっと外してさ、
What kind of bra do you wear?
ブラジャーどんなのして
Oh, it was so cute right now.
あーすごい可愛かった今の
You're wearing a really cute pink bra.
ピンクのすごい可愛いブラジャー着てるね
Pure white skin.
肌真っ白
I want to bite into it.
かじりたいね
Funny that I want to bite into.
かじりたいおかしい
Above, try tsuntsun.
上のさ、ツンツンしてみ
Definitely soft.
柔らかさ確かに
amazing.
すごい
terrible?
やばい?
soft.
柔らかい
Is it a perfect score of 100?
100点満点ですか?
120 points.
120点
Well then, let's do it.
じゃあ、やっちゃおうか
Where did you get this look from?
どこから受けてこんな顔してるの?
It's difficult.
難しいです
When I do something like this, I feel alone.
こういうことするとさ、 いちな気分になっちゃう
yes.
はい
But since it's about Natsu-chan, I thought I'd tease her a little.
でも、夏ちゃんのことさ、 ちょっといじめちゃおうかなと思って
But, is that okay?
んだ けどさ、 いいかな?
yes.
はい
You're nervous.
緊張してるね
Okay, let's go to the hotel.
じゃあ、ホテル行っちゃおう
mosquito.
か
Summer-chan.
夏 ちゃん
yes.
はい
You came to the hotel.
ホテル来ちゃったね
I'm here.
来ちゃいました
How do you feel?
どんな気持ち?
get nervous?
緊張する?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
It's so cute.
すごい可愛いね
You look like an idol.
アイドルみたいな顔してるよね
Have you ever taken a naughty photo shoot like this in a place like this?
こういうとこでさ、 こういうエッチな撮影したことある?
No.
ないです
Not at all?
全くない?
yes.
はい
It's an experience to see.
見経験だね
Are you nervous?
緊張するでしょ?
I'm really nervous.
めっちゃ緊張してます
I will.
するよね
This is amazing.
すごいよ、これ
Pure white.
真っ白で
The uniform looks great on you.
制服すごい似合うね
Have you gotten a boyfriend recently?
最近、彼氏はできた?
Can't you?
できない?
I can't.
できないです
Can't you?
できない?
I'm not here, boyfriend.
いないんだ、彼氏
I'm not there.
いないです
Even though it's so cute.
こんな可愛いのに
No, not at all.
いや、全然
You're popular, right?
モテるでしょ?
I'm not popular.
モテないです
Aren't you popular?
モテないの?
yes.
はい
When you're walking around town, don't you hear someone say something amazing to you?
街歩いてたら、すごい声かけられない?
I can't put it on at all.
全然かけられないです
That's right.
そうなんだ
If this is the case, then it must be a shadow.
これだったら、影じゃなければね
Kuro-chan is cute.
黒ちゃん可愛いよね
Look at this idol face.
見て、このアイドル顔
I'm going to take a lot of pictures of her naked and up there from now on.
今からいっぱいね、裸とかね、あそことか撮っちゃうけど
You're small.
身長ちっちゃいね
what?
何?
How many centimeters is it?
何センチなの?
It is 152 cm.
152センチです
I'm only 152 cm.
152センチしかないんだ
Then, isn't that hole also small?
じゃあ、あそこの穴もちっちゃいんじゃない?
Have you ever been called small?
ちっちゃいって言われたことないの?
be.
ある
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
Aren't your boobs big?
おっぱいも大きくない?
No, it's not big.
いや、大きくないです
How many cups is this?
何カップあんの、これ?
It's a T cup.
Tカップです
A T cup?
Tカップか
He looks like that kid from Nozaka.
飲み坂のあの子に似てるね
Akimoto: I talked to you.
秋元話しちゃったね
What do you enjoy doing these days?
最近は何するのが楽しい?
Lately, I've been having fun playing with friends.
最近は友達と遊ぶのが楽しいです
That's right.
そうなんだ
What do you usually play?
何して遊んでるの、いつも?
I went to dinner.
ご飯行ったり
Do you want to go out to dinner?
ご飯行ったり?
yes.
はい
A stylish face.
オシャレな顔とか
yes.
はい
It's a girl, right?
女子だね、ちゃんと
What do you like about food?
何 が好きなの、ご飯?
I like yakiniku.
焼肉が好きです
It's yakiniku.
焼肉なんだ
It's not like cafes or pancakes.
カフェとかのパンケーキとかじゃないんだ
I don't eat sweets.
甘いの食べないね
甘いの食べないんだ
You look like you're always carrying some amazing ice cream with you.
すごいアイスクリームとか、いつも持ち歩いてそうな顔してるけど
Na.
な
It's just looks, then.
見 た目だけなんだね、じゃあそれは
A carnivorous girl?
肉食女子か
yes.
はい
Do men also eat meat?
男も肉食なの?
I don't have much experience, I guess.
あんまり経験ないよね、多分ね
You're nervous, that's why.
緊張しちゃってるね、だからね
Even her nervous face is so cute.
緊張してる顔もすごい可愛いよ
Let's try unbuttoning this.
この上にさ、ボタン外してみよっか
Okay, go to sleep.
いいよ、寝ちゃって
So cute.
すごい可愛い
Don't you think your breasts will still get bigger?
まだおっぱい大きくなりそうじゃない?
Will it still happen?
まだなりますかね
Kuro-chan gave me a lot of massage today.
今日黒ちゃんにいっぱい揉んでもらったぞ
Maybe we can make it bigger.
大きくできるかもね
That's amazing.
あれがすごいよ
Now, let's unbutton your shirt.
じゃあさ、シャツのボタン取ってみよ
Huh?
っ か
Have a look at the bra?
ブラジャー見してみ?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's pure white.
真っ白だね
I just discovered it at karaoke.
さっきカラオケで発見したんだけどね、
Look.
ほら
That's a naughty place.
えっちゃなとこだね
T-cup breasts.
Tカップのおっぱい
Your skin is really beautiful.
ほんと肌きれいだね
Do you like beauty?
美容好きなの?
yes.
はい
I put on various body creams and things.
いろいろなんかボディークリームとか塗ったりしてるんだ
It's smooth.
すべすべだもんね
Then just turn around and point your butt towards me.
じゃあそのまま後ろを向いて、こっちにお尻を向けてみて
It's cute.
可愛いね
I'll roll it up myself.
自分でまくっちゃうんだ
It's the main body, the main body.
本体だね、本体
Your butt is round.
お尻まん丸だね
How many people have you stationed so far?
今までさ、何人くらい定置したことあるの?
About 3 people.
3人くらい
There are about three people.
3人くらいあるんだ
But that's the only option.
でもそれしかないんだね
It's really cute.
ほんま可愛いの
What's the point of being approached?
言い寄られても何?
Did you refuse?
断ってきたの?
Even now.
今もね
That's right.
そうなんだ
What kind of man do you like?
どういう男の人が好きなの?
kind person.
優しい人
I like people who are kind.
優しい人がいいんだ
Isn't there a face type?
顔のタイプとかないの?
No.
ないです
Isn't there?
ないんだ?
So, is it okay to go with an older uncle?
じゃあ年上のおじさんとかでも結構いける?
yes.
はい
Really?
本当に?
Isn't that a lie?
嘘じゃない?
That's right.
そうなんだ
The strike zone is wide.
ストライクゾーン広いんだね
After that, I always feel like he's my boyfriend.
そ したらいつでも彼氏そうな感じがするけどな
That's not true.
そんなことないんだ
The guard is strong, surprisingly.
ガード硬いんだね、意外に
This one's butt is a little see-through.
ちょっとお尻透けてるよ、これ
How about this, Kuro-chan?
どう黒ちゃん、これ
There's a bit of a dark spot in your pussy.
おまんこのとこちょっとね、くごみあるもんね
Try making your pants look like a T-bag.
自分でパンツさ、Tバッグみたいにしてみて
How about this, Kuro-chan?
どう黒ちゃん、これ
Only 3 people have put their dick in it yet.
3人しかまだチンチン入れてないんだ
That's right.
そうなんだ
Then try standing up once.
じゃあ一回立ってみてよ
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
Let's take a look inside the Blurger.
ちょっとブラージャーの中見てみようか
It makes me nervous.
緊張するね
That's a really beautiful chikubi.
すごい綺麗なチクビだね
I'm already standing for a while.
ちょっとなんかもう立ってるけど
Did the trolley stand up?
トラレット立っちゃった?
I'm nervous and sweating.
緊張して汗かいてる
That's naughty sweat.
エッチな汗だね
Kuro-chan, can you touch my dick?
黒ちゃん、チクビ触ってみ?
Chikubi's feelings?
チクビの気持ち?
Are you not really used to it?
あんまり慣れてないか
I've stood up even more than before.
さっきより凄い立ってきた
What about Kuro-chan and Chikubi?
どう黒ちゃん、チクビは?
soft.
柔らかい
You've never been photographed this close before, right?
こんな近くで撮られたことないでしょ、
Chikubi, like this.
チクビ、こうやって
How does it feel to be touched?
チクビ触られてどんな気分になる?
It makes me feel naughty.
エッチな気分になります
It's going to happen.
なっちゃうんだ
Are you getting wet when you touch me?
チクビ触られてさ、濡れちゃう?
I'm getting wet.
濡れちゃうんだ
I might get wet.
濡れちゃうかも
You're sensitive.
敏感なんだね
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's really cute, though.
すごい可愛いね、でも
A truly beautiful girl.
本当に美少女
Now, turn around and wrap it over your skirt.
じゃあさ、後ろ向いて、 スカート上に巻くって、
Shall I pull up my pants?
パンツ上げてみようか
That's an amazing peach butt.
すごい桃尻だね
Look here.
こっち見て
That's amazing.
すごいね
So why don't you just drop it all the way to the bottom?
じゃあそのまま一番下まで落としてごらん?
If you drop it, spread your legs a little and stick your butt out here.
落としたら、ちょっと足開いて、 こっちにお尻突き出してごら
yeah.
ん
This is naughty.
これは エッチだね
Kuru-chan, aren't you having a bit of a dick reaction?
く る ちゃん、ちょっとチンコ反応しちゃわねえの?
That's the key, because it's still a little hidden.
あそこが鍵になって、まだちょっと隠れてるからね
That's a really beautiful butt.
すごい綺麗なお尻だね
This is perfectly round.
これ、まん丸で
Have you ever been spanked on the butt?
お尻、叩かれたことある?
Penpen.
ペンペンって
There isn't.
ないんだ
So I guess you were kind to me.
じゃあ優しくしてもらったんだね
Everything until now.
今まで全部
I like kind people.
優しい人好きだもんね
So next time, let's do an M shape on the sofa.
じゃあ次は、ソファーの上でM字しようか
First, sit down for PE.
最初、体育座りして
Pick it up slowly.
ゆ っくり拾ってごらん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
It's still growing well today.
今日もちゃんと生えてるんだね
This pussy.
こっちのマンコ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
When it's on top of that, try raising your foot.
その上にかかったら足掲げてみ
Mana-chan's pussy is so beautiful.
マナちゃんのマンコ、すごい綺麗だね
It won't fit a big penis, right?
大きいチンチ入らないんじゃない?
It's so small.
こんなにちっちゃくて
Slow down, let's open your pussy.
ゆっくりさ、おマンコ開いてみようか
Are you embarrassed and wet?
恥ずかしくて濡れちゃった?
Kuro-chan, help me open it more.
黒ちゃん、もっと開くの手伝って
It's small.
ちっちゃいね
You can see even the deep hole.
奥の穴まで映ってるよ
Isn't there a bit of a chestnut standing there too?
ちょっと栗も立ってんじゃないの?
Just a little bit.
少しだけ
It took me all the way to the bottom.
一番奥まで取られちゃったね
Only 3 people have ever been in this one.
3人しか入ったことないもんね、これね
The color is so beautiful.
色 すごい綺麗だもんね
Then, turn around and open the bar to yourself.
そしたら、今度後ろ向いて、自分にバーって開いてみ
The most embarrassing thing.
一番恥ずかしいやって
Look at it as hard as you can.
思いっきり見て
I'll take your butthole too.
お尻の穴も取るよ
Look here.
こっち見てごらん
Her butt is also very open.
お尻もすごい開いてるよ
Please open it more, I think.
もっと開いてごらん、思いっき
the law of nature.
り
How do you feel?
ど んな気分?
This was taken.
これ取られて
It's so embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよね
So let's stand up.
じゃあ立ってみようか
Kuro-chan, would you like to chew on this cute girl?
黒ちゃん、この可愛い子にチューする?
I want to.
したい
It's cute, I want to do it.
可愛いね、したい
Can I have a chew?
チューしていい?
A very naughty face.
すごいエッチャな顔
How about a chew after a long time?
久しぶりのチューどう?
It melted.
とろけました
Melted?
とろけた?
It melted.
とろけちゃった
Her face was so cute now.
今の顔すごい可愛かった
Kuro-chan, what does it taste like?
黒ちゃん、どんな味?
I want to.
したい
Are you going to lick the ground?
地首舐めちゃう?
Shall we do that?
そうしようか
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I've become so angry.
地首ビンビンになっちゃったね
Your face has become so naughty.
なんないエッチな顔になってきたね
Shall I lick this too?
こっちも舐めちゃうか
Your naughty face is cute.
エッチな顔可愛いね
Are you getting wet?
濡れてきちゃう?
I'm getting wet.
濡れてきちゃう
Kuro-chan, check if your pussy is a little wet.
黒 ちゃん、おまんこちょっと濡れてるかチェックしてみて
I know.
知ってる
Wet?
濡れ濡れ?
What kind of smell?
どんな匂い?
It smells a little like sweat.
ちょっと汗の匂いする
It smells good, right?
いい匂いでしょ?
I feel motivated to do something even more embarrassing.
もっと恥ずかしいことしてやる気がするから
Would you like to sit down for a moment?
ちょっと座ってごらん?
Shall I try sleeping in my socks?
靴下寝てみようか
What does it smell like?
どんな匂いする?
Pro-chan.
プロちゃん
That's so embarrassing.
すごい恥ずかしいね
It doesn't smell much.
あんまり匂いしないね
good.
よかった
I'm licking it.
ぺろぺろしてる
Have you ever been licked here?
ここ舐められたことある?
A man?
男の人?
do not have?
ない?
What does this feel like?
どんな感じこれ?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
tickles.
くすぐったい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
気持ちいいの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels a little good.
ちょっと気持ちいい
It hurts though.
痛いけどね
Kuro-chan, isn't it delicious?
クロちゃん、美味しいでしょ?
cute child's feet
可愛い子の足
Wouldn't it be nice if Kuro-chan licked all the sweat off of me?
汗かいた汗、全部クロちゃんに舐めてもらえばいいんじゃない?
Kuro-chan, let's lick the more embarrassing parts.
クロちゃん、もっと恥ずかしいところ舐めようか
Shall we do that?
そうしようか
Mana-chan's sweaty armpits.
マナちゃんの 汗かいた脇を
It might smell good.
いい匂いするかもよ
You look so embarrassed.
すごい恥ずかしい顔してる
It smells sweet.
甘い匂いするね
甘い匂いするんだ
After all, cute girls are sweet, even their sweat is sweet.
やっぱ可愛い子はね、汗も全部甘いの
But the taste is a little salty.
でも味はちょっとしょっぱい
The taste is a little salty.
味はちょっとしょっぱい
copper?
どう?
My armpits were licked.
脇舐められて
This is terrible.
やばいです
A lot of things are terrible.
色々やばい
That's an amazing picture.
すごい絵だね
It hurts so much.
すごく痛い
Kuro-chan, I'm getting excited.
クロちゃん、興奮してきたわ
I'm so excited.
めっちゃ興奮する
Kuro-chan, please stand up.
クロちゃん、立っとくか
I'll try to wet my pants.
俺、パンツ濡らしてみて
Long time no see.
久しぶりのチンチン
get nervous?
緊張する?
Do you watch it often?
よく見てる?
Take a closer look at this.
近くで見て、これ
copper?
どう?
Try squeezing it with your hand.
手でツンツンしてみ
Touch me gently, okay?
優しく触るんじゃね?
Look at that slowly.
それ、ゆっくり見て
Try making it bigger.
大きくしてみ、それ
Really, take a close look.
ほんと、近くで見てみ
It's getting bigger and bigger, Chin Chin.
だんだん大きくなってきたよ、チンチン
close.
近い
It's close.
近いね
It's grown so big.
こんな大きくなったわ
Kuro-chan, what do you think?
クロちゃん、どう?
For such a cute child.
こんな可愛い子に
Please give me a good squeeze.
チンチンしこしこしてもらって
Highest.
最高
copper?
どう?
this.
これ
It's gotten so big.
こんな大きくなっちゃったね
hard.
硬い
Do you like hard cocks?
硬いチンチン好き?
yes.
はい
Let's slowly play this.
ゆっくりこれ、テロピロしてみ
What does it taste like?
どんな味?
I don't taste it.
味しない
Didn't you taste it?
味しなかった?
Try licking the tip of the tip.
さきっぽのカリのところなめてみ
Slowly, let's add some plagiarism.
ゆっくりさ、パクって加えちゃおうか
It's crazy to stand up like that.
そんなエッチの立てるとヘロい
hey.
ね
A hard cock is delicious, isn't it?
硬 いチンチン美味しいでしょ?
Let's have a lot more sex.
もっといっぱいエッチの立ってみ
It got really intense.
すーごいギンギンになっちゃったね
Add it all the way to the bottom.
一番奥まで加えてみ
To the point where it hurts.
苦しいところまで
You ate a lot, Chin Chin.
すごい食べたね、チンチン
Yeah.
うん
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Try licking the back.
裏のところなめてみ
A place that feels good.
気持ちいいところ
Stand up, stick your butt out and lick it.
立って、お尻突き出してなめてみ
What does it smell like?
どんな匂いする?
There.
そこ
Don't smell it.
匂いしないで
From the balls to the top.
タマタマから上までベロって
Pro-chan feels good, right?
プロちゃん気持ちいいでしょ?
Try ripping off the balls.
タマをパクってしてみ
Have you ever licked a place like that?
そんなところ舐めたことある?
Not really.
ないですね
It feels weird.
変な感じだね
Pro-chan, Mana-chan's.
プ ロちゃん、 マナちゃんのさ、
Don't you want to see it up close?
お前近くで見たくない?
I want to see it.
見たい
Shall we take a look?
見ちゃおうか
Right in front of this face.
この顔の真ん前に
straddle
またがって
difference.
さ
Struggle to be safe.
が ばって無事して
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Wow, so wet.
うわ、すごい濡れ濡れ
Highest.
最高
This is amazing.
すごいね、これ
It's so hot.
めちゃくちゃイッチ
Yes, amazing.
そう、すごい
So that you can see all the way to the back.
しばん奥まで見れるように
This is Rourke's chance.
ロークのチャンスだね
Highest.
最高
Look, it's dripping all over.
てっかで汁垂れてるよ、ほら
From the pussy.
まんこから
I got excited.
興奮しちゃったんだ
Valmier.
バルミエ
It's difficult, seeing it so close.
難しいね、こんな近くで見られちゃったね
This pussy is sticky to Kuro-chan's mouth.
このおまんこさ、 黒ちゃんの口んとこにベタって
Does your pussy feel good?
おまんこ気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Please lick me more and more.
もっといっぱいベロベロ舐めてね
Do you want to taste the pussy?
おまんこの味する?
Yeah.
うん
Have the tongue fully inserted into the hole.
ベロいっぱい入れてもらう、穴に
Mana-chan, have I ever done this to you?
マナちゃんさ、 お前にしたことある?
Is there some?
ちょっとある?
Have you ever used a phone?
電話使ったことあるよね?
Please show it to me in front of Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃんの前でさ、 見せてみてよ
Give me a call.
電話をね
Can you do it?
できるかな?
Would you like to try it?
やってみる?
Show me a lot of yourself, Kuro-chan.
お まえいっぱい見せてね、黒ちゃん
It's Chimchin on the neck.
首のチムチンだ
It's dripping so much juice.
すごい汁垂れてるよ
Kuro-chan, does anyone know?
黒ちゃん、誰か知ってる?
This close
こんな近く
Even if you're seen, what have you done?
で 見られても、 何したことないでしょ?
Kuro-chan, it's a pussy pack.
黒ちゃん、おまんこパックって
It's about time for Anko.
そろそろあんこ
That's what I like about Surisuri.
そこスリスリ好きなんだよ
It's really wet, look.
すごい濡れの中だよ、ほら
Full of Chimchin.
チムチンでいっぱい
Show me the nearest prince.
一番近くの太子見せてね
Please take a look.
い っぱい見してね
It's so wet.
め ちゃくちゃ濡れてるよ
Kuro-chan, her pussy is completely fried.
黒ちゃん、 いったおまんこもいっきり焼いてる
Your pussy is twitching.
ヒクヒクしてるね、おまんこね
I'm gone.
い っちゃったんだ
When you cut it out, it stands out.
くりとりするとピンピン立ってる
how was it?
どうだった?
So close.
こんな近くで
It was embarrassing.
恥ずかしかったね
So next time, let's lick each other.
じゃあ次は、 なめあいっこしようか
Kuro-chan, turn your head towards me.
黒ちゃん、あたまあっちに向けて
Then I'll take off the skirt.
そしたらスカートとっちゃおうか、
Here.
ここで
I sewed it.
縫いちゃった
縫いちゃったね
Slowly lick it.
ゆっくりぺろぺろして
I like the uramen noodles there.
そこの裏なめんの好きなの
It's really hard to describe.
すっごいえっちゃなめがたい
Lick your dick.
チンチンパンパンなめ
Your pussy feels good too, right?
おまんこも気持ちいいでしょ?
It's full of dicks.
チンチンでいっぱいだね
It's now bigger than Manachi's face.
ま なちの顔より大きくなっちゃったね
Kuro-chan, let's put some dick in there.
黒ちゃん、 チンチン入れちゃおうか
Let's do that.
そうしよう
Manachi-chan lying down.
まなちちゃんの横ろがって
I wonder if I can take off my bra.
ブラジャー取れるかな、それ
It stung, you see.
刺さったよ、ほら
Wow,
うわ、
Look, it's full of juice.
ほ ら、汁いっぱいついてる、ほ
and others.
ら
What do you think, Chin Chin?
どう、 チンチン?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Her face is so cute with dick in it.
チンチン入れられてる顔すっごいかわいいね
Look, it's deep inside.
ほら、刺さってる奥まで
Kuro-chan, follow me all the way.
黒ちゃん、奥までついてみ
To the deepest part.
一番奥まで
What, this big penis?
どう、このおっきなチンチン
It feels so good.
気持ちよすぎ
Does it feel too good?
気持ちよすぎ?
Kuro-chan, come down here for a moment.
黒ちゃん、ちょっとこの下になって
Manachi-chan, move.
まなちちゃん、動きな
It really stings.
すごい刺さってるよ
Well, get behind me.
じゃ、後ろに手ついてさ
Kuro-chan from below.
黒ちゃん、下から
Here you go, tsubo tsubo.
ほら、つぼつぼ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Look, the very back, come out to the back and look.
ほら、一番後ろ、後ろに出てきてほら
So, lift your hips up.
じゃ、腰浮かしてみ
Just with your feet.
ちょっと足で
That's also Kuro-chan, following from below.
それも黒ちゃん、ついて下から
oh
お
stomach.
腹
It's stuck deep inside
奥 まで刺さってる
hey.
ね
Well then, next.
じゃ、 次さ
I was so excited.
ピヨーンってなって
Now, Manachi-chan, let's do this.
今は、 まなちちゃん、この手ついて
Then, stick your hips out.
で、腰を白々に突き出してこい
Kuro-chan, please follow me more.
黒ちゃん、もっとついてみ
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
One, I have a lot of them at the moment.
1つ、今のとこ、いっぱいついて
Looks like it's going to go away.
いっちゃいそう
quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly
早く、早く、早く、早く、
quickly.
早 く
Have you ever done anything like this?
こんなにやってることある?
first time.
初めて
Look where it's coming in.
入ってるところ、ほら
I'll take it all.
全部、いっちゃう
It looks like it's biting me.
すぼすぼ刺さってるようだ
Are you going again?
また、いっちゃうの?
Kuro-chan, that's it for the last time.
黒ちゃん、じゃ、最後
The back is bulky!
バック、もっかいしよっ
mosquito.
か
Now, Chi-chan, hold my hand.
今 のちちゃん、手を持って
At first, ask them to take it slow.
最初、ゆっくりついてもらう
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Oku, do you go when you're tired?
奥、疲れると、いっちゃうの?
Kuro-chan, pull me over.
黒ちゃん、じゃ、引っ張って
It's going to get hard.
ガンガンついちゃう
Kuro-chan, please follow me more and more.
黒ちゃん、もっと、いっぱいついて
Ah, let's go
あー、いっちゃ
cormorant.
う
Slowly, go all the way.
ゆ っくり、奥までついて
Do it gradually and quickly.
だんだん、早く、しちゃって
Kuro-chan, be beautiful every day.
黒ちゃん、一日に、きれいちゅう
Kuro-chan, open it up as hard as you can.
黒ちゃん、思いっきり、開いて、こら
I let out a lot of it inside.
中、出しちゃったね、いっぱい
Take a look at it to your heart's content.
思いっきり、見てみして
There's still a lot left.
まだ、いっぱい、いっちゃったね
This is the first time I've gone like this.
初めて、こんなに、いっちゃった
I felt good.
気持ちがった
It was my first time to go like this.
初めて、こんなに、いったんだ
Great, it's gone.
すごい、いっちゃったよ
Finally, Chinchinsa.
最後、ちんちんさ
Would you like me to clean it for you?
きれいにしてもらおうか
Clean everything.
全部、きれいにして
Let's clean it from the inside out.
一番、奥まで、きれいにしてもらおう
There are a lot of naughty sounds coming out.
いっぱい、えっちな音が出ておる
Was it clean?
きれいにできた?
I tried shaking, and finally.
ふるふるしてみ、最後
It was beautifully done.
きれいにできたね
Kuro-chan was so cute,
黒ちゃん、すごい、かわいかったよ、
today.
今日
It was my first time, and I was nervous, but
初めてだったけどさ、 緊張したけど、
You did your best.
がんばったね
Awesome, nice.
すごい、いいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
See you again, Manazu-chan.
また会おうね、まなずちゃん
Thank you again.
また、お願いします
Kuro-chan, I want to meet you too.
黒ちゃんも、会いたいよね
Yeah, I want to see you again.
うん、また会いたい
Thank you, Manazu-chan.
まなずちゃん、ありがとうございます
thank you.
ありがとうございます
bye bye.
バイバイ